{"data":[{"question":"Robin's family ___ poetry lovers.","a":"are all","b":"all are","c":"are being","d":"is","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Collective nouns such as family,team and staff may be either singular or plural depending on their use in the sentence. \n- In this case \"family\" acts as plural","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"A dozen _________ twelve, and two ___ twenty-four.","a":"Is, dozens are","b":"is, dozen is","c":"is, dozens is","d":"is, dozen are","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Two\/three\/four ...dozen: singular noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"It was reported that ten ___ including an infant.","a":"was killing","b":"was killed","c":"had killed","d":"were killed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Subject (ten= ten persons) is singular \n- Passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Deer ___ faster than dogs.","a":"runs","b":"run","c":"will run","d":"are running","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Deer: plural noun \n- Simple present tense: express general facts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Steam and ice ___ two of the three forms of water.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"were","d":"was","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Use a plural verb with two or more subjects when they are connected by and.\n- Simple present tense: express general facts\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"The whole nation _________ greatly moved by President's words.","a":"is","b":"was","c":"were","d":"had","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Collective nouns such as family,team and staff may be either singular or plural depending on their use in the sentence. \n- In this case \"The whole nation\" acts as singular \n- Simple past tense ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"The students in our school each ___ an electronic dictionary.","a":"had","b":"has","c":"are having","d":"have","answer":"4","explain":"\n- If the word \"each\" comes before a compound subject, use the singular. \n ex: each boy and girl has flowers. \n- If the word \"each\" comes after a plural subject, use the plural verb \n ex: boys and girls each have flowers.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"0nly one answer ___ to the question.","a":"has been given","b":"have been given","c":"had given","d":"was given","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Passive voice \n- Subject (only one) is singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"The girl sitting by the door is the only one of the students in our class who ___ from the countryside.","a":"were","b":"are","c":"is","d":"was","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Sometimes the pronoun who, that, or which is the subject of a verb in the middle of the sentence. The pronouns who, that, and which become singular or plural according to the noun directly in front of them. So, if that noun is singular, use a singular verb. If it is plural, use a plural verb. \n- Who= the girl sitting by the door","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Most of the mistakes ___ because of carelessness.","a":"are made","b":"were made","c":"were making","d":"has been made","answer":"1","explain":"- With words that indicate portions - percent, fraction, part, majority, some, all, none, remainder, and so forth - look at the noun in your of phrase (object of the preposition) to determine whether to use a singular or plural verb. If the object of the preposition is singular, use a singular verb. If the object of the preposition is plural, use a plural verb.\n- Mistakes: plural noun.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"}]}